Hey, get over here.
Hey!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Hey.
Do you get a kick out of
picking on the weak?
Huh? Who the hell are you?
You got a problem, do ya?
Just go away.
Shinjo, I heard
you're a tae kwon do champion. Yes?
I…
Will you be my teacher?
Too late, I've quit that.
Shinjo, I want
to get stronger.
Oh, shit.
This guy, he's gonna kill Shimura.
I don't like the police.
No one's getting in my way.
Don't you dare.
Leave him be.
Shimura!
That's enough! Tell him to go!
Is he important to you?
If he is…
…you'd better protect him.
Now he can't use his calf kick.
You've done enough! Please listen!
He's trying to kill you, Shimura!
Don't interfere.
Shinjo. Satisfied?
Forcing my friend
to watch me get my ass kicked.
You aren't
a psychopath.
Let's be real.
You're jealous…
of us.
You son of a bitch.
Kanegon is the…
only friend I've ever had.
I will never forgive you…
for hurting my friend
You shut the fuck up!
Shimura!
The stream must stop, Kanegon.
This is the end.
The channel… is mine.
Stop it, now.
What? It's been over a while.
Please. End it. No more.
-I told you I'm not…
-Come on, can't you see?
Shimura!
HE STOOD UP!
GET HIM, SHIMURA!
How an amateur…
…can beat…
Oh, my.
You're really crazy.
…a Tae kwon do fighter.
You will die if you keep doing this.
Rule one.
All right
I will kill you.
Just die!
How an amateur can beat
a tae kwon do fighter.
Rule one…
is to steal their kicks.
Everything leads up to this technique.
Grab onto the back of their collar
like you're holding a bag
and lift them on to your shoulder.
Wow! Baseball choke!
Go.
WHOAAAAAA!!
DON'T LOOSEN YOUR GRIP!
Yes, Shimura!
Knock out. Shimura won!
Yes!
Shimura you won!
Pull him! He's knocked out!
The fight is over.
-You have to stop!
-Shimura!
-Hey!
If you don't let go, he'll die!
Shimura!
Hey! Come here.
You did it!
You're really something.
Hey.
TAE KWON DO TOURNAMENT
WINNER REO SHINJO
CHAMPION
TAE KWON DO TOURNAMENT
-Did I say you could touch it?
-Sorry.
Shinjo, you really are incredible.
I suck at everything I do.
I hope I can become a champion like you.
-Last one.
-Let's go.
Thank you.
-Hmm?
-Huh?
Take it.
No, Shinjo, this, this is yours.
Forget it. Put it on and try
to get a little stronger.
Are you sure?
Thank you so much.
I'll cherish it until I die.
Takuma is
at the former Ikebe factory site.
Takuma!
Hey!
Hang in there!
I'm sorry I couldn't be strong enough.
Hey.
Wake up!
I said… Wake up!
Takuma!
Hey, let's get out of here.
He'll kill us if he wakes up.
We can't. He's passed out.
Whoa!
What the hell are you doing?
Wait, listen.
He went a little overboard, that's all.
Hey? No, I was desperate and I…
I never want to see your face again.
Oh… my.
That bastard is crazy.
He was… crying.
What?
What are you talking about? As if.
-Uh…
-By the way, is your foot okay?
Uh, I think so.
Yeah?
WAY MORE INTENSE THAN BAD FELLOWS!
DON'T COMPARE THIS TO THAT STAGED SHOW
VIRAL HIT IS THE REAL DEAL
BAD FELLOWS IS WASHED-UP
I'm terribly sorry.
If only I had… dealt with them properly
It doesn't matter.
In fact, now…
things are getting interesting.
He won. He did great.
Oh, thank God.
Is he hurt?
I wonder if he's okay.
He took a beating, but he should be fine.
You're worried about a boy?
IS HE HURT?
HE TOOK A BEATING
It's because you're involved with him.
All those videos are circulating.
HOT GIRLFRIEND!
Well, you won't see him again.
Why?
Why can't I see him?
Because he has no use
in your future whatsoever.
-Not true.
-Asamiya!
You mustn't plan to see him again.
I won't.
I promise
BARBER YASHIO
1,012,054 SUBSCRIBERS
We hit a million subscribers!
What the hell?
Yes!!
Aki, Aki! What did we make?
This time we got…
Wow!
1.78 million!
Wait a minute. That means we raked in…
1,068,000 yen in one stream.
We made over a million yen!
Our revenue to date is 2.3 million.
Good on you!
Ah!
AMOUNT DUE: 3.14M YEN
Do you suppose we can do it again?
Oh, for sure we can.
We're one of the popular streamers now.
Our time is finally here.
Are you excited?
Of course I am!
You'll see why at school, okay?
Look! There's Shimura!
Well, how does this feel?
Yeah, it's not bad.
Listen up.
This is
what the view from the top is like.
You know, this is great.
I mean, the view.
It's better at the top, you know.
What? What do you mean?
Have you gone crazy?
Hey, I followed your official account.
Follow me back?
Can you follow me back too?
You repulse me.
Turning to the Internet for friends?
I'm joking!
She said yes!
I watch your channel every day!
We're going to crash!
What's wrong? Aren't you gonna buy them?
Well, they're really…
You need more shoes.
You are allowed to buy it.
Right, Aki?
People have free will. Let him decide.
Of course, but… well…
You'll tell Asamiya you like her,
won't you?
Mm!
Well, it would be rude
to confess to her with such ratty shoes.
Don't you think? Yeah?
Oh! What's going on here?
It's just a present.
Wait, is it for me?
Shimura.
Don't worry about it.
I got a bonus.
No, it's not that.
You're not doing anything illegal?
Huh?
Are you scamming people?
Uh no, why would you think that?
Oh, that's good!
Oh, thank you.
-I'll cherish it.
-Mm! Hmm!
So cute.
Thanks for the meal.
-But you've barely touched your food.
-I'm not hungry.
-Are you getting sick?
-No.
Then what's wrong?
Don't tell me you have a crush on someone.
Hey, is it the blonde guy
or the black-haired guy? Which one?
That's harassment, you know.
I'll be
back to work starting tomorrow.
Can we walk home together after work?
So what's this simple job?
Well…
Here.
Pick anyone.
CLIENT LIST
BUSINESS OWNER
CHIEF DIRECTOR
I don't… get it.
These are all… our important sponsors.
-Yes?
-It's Watanabe.
I'm sorry to make you wait.
Work went overtime.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
That's all right.
Everyone is on their first time.
It's what I like.
Here, have a drink. Hmm?
It's tea?
What made you think I'd let you?
Alcohol for someone underage?
You know, I have a daughter
who's the same age as you.
What?
And all she does
is waste time on being in love.
She should just listen to
all the wise things I say to her.
But…
you'll listen
to everything that I say to you.
Right? Hmm?
Hmm.
She quit?
You didn't know about that?
Well, she quit about a month ago.
It's been a really tough month,
so no more long vacations for you, got it?
Oh, by the way,
Shimura you're a streamer, aren't you?
UNREAD
To tell you the truth,
I was thinking about
trying out streaming myself.
Hey!
What, you're taking off again?
I won't.
I promise
In exchange,
I have a favor to ask.
Shimura's mom must be
exempt from medical fees.
Please!
Shimura?
Stop it!
Here! Here!
Give it back to me!
Try and get this!
Let's go.
What's wrong?
They threw away my key chain.
Shimura! What are you doing?
I'll catch up later.
Don't be upset. We'll find it.
There it is! I found it!
Thank you!
Asamiya!
What are you doing here?
You'll be late for your recital.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
See you soon!8
Hey!
Is Shimura with you?
He's not coming.
His mom had to go to hospital.
Here. Shimura told me to give it to you.
Hey, there's
a cabbage white butterfly over there.
-Let's go!
BE STRONGER!
VIRAL_HIT
BAD FELLOWS gave us an offer?
Yeah, it's crazy!
I got a DM from their management.
They said they want us
to meet Mr. Kuwata and talk!
Is it real though?
Look for yourself.
BAD FELLOWS
It's real?
Told you it's real.
I have met him… before.
What? When?
Before my Shinjo match.
-Where?
-At my home.
Huh. About what?
He wanted me to fight on his show.
Why didn't you tell me?
I wasn't interested.
You idiot!
This is a huge offer.
BAD FELLOWS would make us
even more famous!
Maybe I'll hear him out.
Nice. You're motivated now.
I don't know what had gotten into you.
Nothing. I just wanna make money quickly.
That's the spirit.
That's what I like to hear.
I'll set up a meeting for you.
ROPPONGI
What a fancy place.
He messaged us. Don't be intimidated.
Sorry to keep you waiting. After you.
I am so honored.
The famous Viral Hit came
all this way to see me.
No. Thank you so much for the DM.
Um, I hear you had
already offered Shimura to participate
in the BAD FELLOWS tournament.
Yeah.
Okay, well, we will consider it
depending on the opponent
you choose for us. Yes?
I think that you're confused.
What?
Well, handing you a role
in our BAD FELLOWS tournament
was not my plan.
But we're interested
in acquiring Viral Hit.
It's true, isn't it? You need money.
Wait just a minute.
There's no way we can agree to this.
Viral Hit is our channel.
We won't give it away.
She's right, we can't sell it.
These childish games won't work forever.
-Huh? What did you say?
-Kanegon.
Could it be you feel threatened
because we're getting popular?
Threatened?
Any moment, your channel can disappear.
What should I be worried about?
How about you remember where you belong.
This is ridiculous.
Let's go.
Tell me, how are you going?
Each day it changes.
And, my body often feels heavy.
But I have to try and get well for my son.
This cardigan… was a present from him.
I have called you here…
to talk about your son.
My son?
Shimura?
Your son has been making money
by fighting.
He's fighting?
And because of your son,
my daughter, she was publicly humiliated.
There are false rumors on social media
that they are seeing each other.
Even her face is exposed.
It's very troubling for us.
I'll waive your medical expenses.
Hey?
In return, your son…
must never visit my daughter again.
Sorry for the trouble
my son has caused you all.
I'm truly sorry.
But…
I can't make that promise.
Who he wants to see…
and who he wants to talk to…
it's not my right to decide that for him.
-What happened to your face?
-Huh?
Oh, you weren't fighting
with anyone were you?
No, I would never do that.
Don't worry about it. I got a bonus.
That guy was a real asshole.
Since it's come to this,
let's take down BAD FELLOWS by ourselves.
But that guy seemed to know
that Shimura was in need of more money.
Mm. He also knows where I live.
Well, it's fine.
We won't have anything to do with him.
Let's find our next opponent.
-Huh?
-What is it?
-The hell is this?
-What?
They banned our account.
SUSPENDED
Huh?
What the hell is going on?
I don't know, I don't know.
Wait, what if I try to open it again?
Kanegon, what is it?
Look at this.
NEW PARTNERSHIP
The platform we're using
and Kuwata's company
formed a business partnership?
He did this. That bastard!
Why did you leave?
You left our important sponsor behind.
Sponsor?
-You tried to pimp me out.
-Rumi, that's no way to put things.
It's an important part
of business hospitality, you know?
I don't get it.
Enough.
I quit.
If it's like this, I'll go it alone.
Well, maybe.
But the thing is…
What?
You haven't met your quota
and your contract isn't up yet.
If you're going to go,
there's a penalty to pay.
Can you afford that?
That's what I thought.
Okay, fine.
How about online? Hmm?
You won't have to sleep with old men,
and you can edit your face
so no one will recognize you.
Well?
Sorry.
I have to go home.
Where are you going?
Huh?
To the cops?
Is that… a good idea?
You think?
This will end up on the Internet.
What are you doing over there?
You're not doing
something bad again, are you?
Your agency was behind it?
It wasn't you that had
those two guys attack Shimura?
No.
We're in the same agency,
but I've never met them.
And you didn't get me drunk
and steal our password?
Uh, I apologize for the password.
I'm sorry.
Ah, jeez.
But why would the president do that?
Our agency falls…
under the BAD FELLOWS group is why.
Huh?
He DM'd me to get close to Viral Hit,
I suppose.
Really? You think so?
He was looking for Viral Hit.
He seemed to be
under the big boss's thumb.
I don't know if I can trust you.
After all that you put me through.
I'm sorry.
Fine, I'll trust you.
All right.
Let's go fix this.
We'll go to the police
and tell them everything.
So is it really bad?
She's been undergoing radiation therapy.
It's not working.
And the immunotherapy,
I may be able to give you the money soon.
Uh, look, in her current condition,
it just wouldn't be effective.
So, what?
Uh, what… what can be done for her?
Well, there is iron radiotherapy.
-Use it. Please.
-It's a very expensive treatment.
Yes, okay. I'll work and pay for it.
We would do it several times
to see if it was effective.
How much is it?
In total,
somewhere around ten million.
So much.
However, we do understand
your family situation.
The director suggested to your mother
she could be exempt
from the medical expenses, but…
What?
Are you okay, Mom?
I'm okay.
Don't look so sad.
I was shocked.
I didn't know what you were doing.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about saying
who would watch your stream.
It's so popular.
You have many fans on there.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
I have to say…
I don't really like seeing you
get beaten up like that.
Even less, do I like
you beating someone else.
You're right.
But it's strange…
Somehow,
I did feel good.
My son, who always seemed a bit fragile,
looked strong.7
I thought
he might be okay,
even if I'm not around anymore.
Why do you say that?
Mm…
I'm just telling you my thoughts.
Moshi moshi.
Shimura.
It was all Kuwata's doing after all.
And the ban wasn't it.
He was… targeting us from the very start.
So, what is it?
It was you, wasn't it?
You got Viral Hit's account banned.
I told you,
you should remember your place.
I know what you've been doing
behind the scenes.
So, what do I care?
We can expose you in a video
anytime we want.
Fine, go do it.
What do you think of this instead?
I'll give you
a fight purse of a million yen.
Consider it. This will be
your last chance to work for me.
What do you mean by that?
-We're not going to agree--
-No. This simplifies it.
If I make an appearance now,
it'll generate buzz.
This is my proposal.
-I want to fight.
-Shimura!
I don't want your money.
For this, in exchange, I want donations.
Donations?
We'll divide into a red and a blue corner
and viewers will donate
to the side they want to support.
BAD FELLOWS will be
the ones streaming the match.
It's a good deal, isn't it?
The rules, then.
BAD FELLOWS' own rules.
Three five-minute rounds.
Will that work for you?
I think it does.
Works for me.
I will find an opponent
that's worthy of you.
There's no need to do that.
You'll be the one fighting.
You bastard. Who do you think you are?
The BAD FELLOWS representative.
Wouldn't this match
get them the most attention this way?
Or are you afraid
that you're less popular
and the donations will expose it?
Very well.
Let's do it. Me and you.
Donations?
Our account may be banned,
but we've got a million fans.
What if they all donated?
Ten million could be done.
Nice going, Shimura!
-What a brilliant idea!
-Gross! Get off me!
Okay, let's strategize
how we can appeal to our fans
in a meeting at Aki's house.
Oh, I can't. I have plans.
-You what?
-Just some errands.
I came to return this.
I'll leave you be.
Account got banned, didn't it?
Yeah.
Why was that?
BAD FELLOWS is the reason.
And now,
Shimura's planning to fight the big boss.
Kuwata.
I wouldn't do that.
Why shouldn't he?
TEACH HIM A LIFE LESSON!
PUNISH THE DISRESPECTFUL BRATS!
Runs in my bones
Scream under the light, this moment…
Mm.
Hey!
Watch this.
What?
VIRAL HIT PRODUCER
CAUGHT UNDERAGE DRINKING
No way.
Is that Kanegon?
Look at this.
-Is that him?
-Kanegon!
SO FULL OF HIMSELF
THEIR ACCOUNT DESERVES TO BE BANNED
A HIGH-SCHOOL DRUNK LOL
A WOMANIZING BRAT
Viral Hit is facing major backlash.
The channel launched
in February this year.
It became popular for showing real fights
picked by a high school student
and has earned lots of money
from donations.
However, the producer's drinking video
has gone viral
and is facing major backlash.
The channel is facing
a storm of criticism.
Their fighter is
high school student Kota Shimura.
BLOOD MONEY LOL
Producer and cameraman is Toru Kaneko.
I WANT MY MONEY BACK
The editor is a female student
who attends the same school.
VIRAL HIT IS FINISHED
ARREST INEVITABLE
Damn it. This must be his doing.
Kuwata must be pulling the strings.
Kuwata is a former MMA champion
in underground fighting.
How do you know that?
Shinjo told me.
-Shinjo told you?
-And that's not all.
He saw Kuwata at the scene
where his friend died.
Shinjo is convinced
that Kuwata is the murderer.
What does this all mean?
Shinjo got a call
on the day his friend was killed.
The caller told him
where his friend was being attacked.
But it was a trap to frame Shinjo.
-Why would Kuwata kill Shinjo's friend?
-I don't know.
But… this proves
how dangerous Kuwata really is.
So we can't expect a lot of donations.
We should back out of the fight.
Well, what else can I do here?
You know I need the money.
I have no way to make money any other way.
I really have no choice left.
Hmm.
This is the real deal!
It's Viral Hit!
Hey! Don't film us without permission.
-You gotta get owned!
-Too late!
Get lost!
We… stand out when we're together.
Let's separate now,
and if anything happens, call me. Got it?
GOODBYE NORMAL LIFE LOL
YOU'VE BEEN COMMITTING A CRIME
WHO THINKS OF MAKING MONEY
THROUGH VIOLENCE? LOL
I BET THE POLICE ARE ONTO THEM
THEY WON'T GET AWAY WITH THIS
TREMBLE WITH FEAR
PAY US BACK
I'LL KILL YOU
HE'S THAT POOR?
MOM'S HOSPITALIZED
BAD PARENTING
CLASS SHOWS
YOU'RE DEAD, SHIMURA
A CRIMINAL LIVES HERE
PAY US BACK
This must be where Shimura lives.
GOLD DIGGER
KANEGON'S THE MASTERMIND
I'LL KILL KANEGON WITHIN A WEEK
I'LL HUNT YOU DOWN
DIE
YOUR ACCOUNT HAS BEEN SUSPENDED
THIS IS VIRAL HIT'S SCHOOL
DROP DEAD SHIMURA!
DIE, KANEGON
There's no point.
Kaneko won't even answer his phone.
I see.
I can try calling him later.
Yeah, please do.
Are you… doing okay?
Mmm.
No turning back
It's too late.
Be careful.
I will.
And, you.
Yeah.
Well, see you later.
AKI YASHIO
Kuwata is a former MMA champion
in underground fighting.
It's true, isn't it? You need money.
In total, somewhere around ten million.
It's okay.
I've got TOU-KEI.
NEWTUBE HOW_TO_FIGHT
What?
What's going on?
THIS CHANNEL HAS BEEN DELETED
-I'm going out.
-What?
Where are you going so late?
I'm not going to let this happen.
Aki!
Logan.
Where are you, TOU-KEI?
I have no way of winning without you.
Who's out there?
It's Asamiya.
What?
So, what do you want?
Hey.
Please
don't take Viral Hit from us.
That channel…
it's a very important place for us.
It's because we had that channel
that all of us were saved.
So, please…
Please, I'm begging you.
Please give us back Viral Hit.
What is it?
I saw the hate
that you were getting online.
Oh. Mm.
You turned down the offer
to waive your mother's medical fees.
-Mm.
-I asked my dad.
But in return,
I said I wouldn't see you again.
No.
If you don't have to worry
about the medical fees,
you won't have to fight anymore.
-Then, you won't get hate online--
-But I really can't accept that.
Because I don't want to stop seeing you.
Besides,
it's not… just for money.
I don't want to give it up.
Everything we built together.
If I say no,
what then?
If you intend to crush us,
we won't go easy on you either.
Oh, I see!
You still don't understand, do you?
Everything you have,
that you've built with sweat and tears,
I can crush in a single day.
No. In just a matter of minutes even.
Everything you've built up to this point,
was that insignificant in the end.
You're going to do it
no matter what, right?
But…
you won't get
any more videos from TOU-KEI.
What? How?
How did you know about his videos?
I sent them.
The videos were sent by me.
What?
Oh, Viral Hit… is already dead.
It can't end.
I won't let it.
I'll protect it no matter what!
Let me go! Let me go! I said let me go!
The videos? I don't understand.
There are videos on there.
And I've been sending them to you.
BE STRONGER!
NEWTUBE @VIRAL_HIT
Wait, so you know who TOU-KEI is?
No, this isn't even mine.
What?
Then…
was someone else watching those videos?
BE STRONGER!
NEWTUBE @VIRAL_HIT
Let go of me.
I said
let go of me!
You little…
Don't hold back.
I am the original Viral Hit.
VIRAL HIT